Here's some code that draws a square.
这里有一些代码绘制一个正方形
Notice how we're using the same lines over and over again here,
注意我们如何用同样的线路在这里
and that's just for a square with four sides.
而这只是一个四方面的正方形
What if we wanted to draw a shape with say a 100 sides?
如果我们想画出一个 100 面的形状呢 ?
That's a lot of work and it turns out it's not necessary.
那是很多工作 结果没有必要
Using a four loop,
用一个四环
we can draw a shape having as many sides as we
我们可以画出像我们一样多边的形状
want and it will only take three lines of code.
只需要三行代码
To create a for loop,
要创建 for 循环
we start with a line like this;
我们从这样的线开始
for side in [1, 2,
在 [ 1  2
3, 4]: then we follow it with the code that we want to loop or repeat.
3   4 ): 然后我们用我们想要循环或重复的代码来关注它
Notice how we indented these lines by moving them four spaces to the right.
请注意 我们如何将这些线条缩进到右边的四个空格
This is how we show that these lines are inside the loop.
这就是我们展示这些线在循环中的方式
In other words, it's these indented lines that will get run repeatedly.
换句话说 就是这些缩进的线 会反复运行
So, this code will run multiple times,
所以这个代码会运行多次
but how many times?
但有多少次
Well, notice the four something in something else structure in this line.
好吧 请注意这一行中其他结构中的四个东西
Essentially, it is saying run the code in
基本上它是说运行代码
this loop one time for each of the things in this list.
对于此列表中的每个内容 此循环一次
Since there are four items in the list,
由于列表中有四个项目
the loop runs four times.
循环运行四次
For this particular loop,
对于这个特殊的回路
it doesn't really matter what the items in the list are.
不重要的是清单里的物品是什么
We could change these numbers or even replace them with strings.
我们可以更改这些数字 甚至可以用字符串替换它们
Again, the loop runs one time for each item in the list
再次 该循环对列表中的每个项运行一次
and it's because there are four items in the list that the loop will run four times.
因为列表中有 4 个项目 循环会运行 4 次